<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
 Copyright 2016 The TensorFlow Authors. All Rights Reserved.

 Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
 you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
 You may obtain a copy of the License at

     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
 distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
 WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
 See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
 limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>

    <string name="description_info">Info</string>
    <string name="request_permission">This sample needs camera permission.</string>
    <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_history">HistoryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>


    <!--in EditCamera-->
    <string name="timestamp_not_available">not available</string>
    <string name="no_comment">no comments available</string>
    <string name="timestamp_text">Camera captured on:</string>
    <string name="upload_text">Camera upload on:</string>
    <string name="comment_text">Comments:</string>
    <string name="angle_text">Angle (from horizontal):</string>


    <string name="type_text">Type:</string>
    <string name="area_text">Area:</string>
    <string name="mount_text">Mounted on:</string>
    <string name="direction_text">Direction:</string>
    <string name="height_text">Height (m):</string>


    <!-- App and toolbar labels-->
    <string name="app_label">unsurv</string>
    <string name="history_label">History</string>
    <string name="detector_label">Detect Cameras</string>
    <string name="map_label">Map</string>
    <string name="statistics_label">Statistics</string>
    <string name="settings_label">Settings</string>
    <string name="organize_label">Scan your city</string>
    <string name="manual_capture_label">Manual Capture</string>
    <string name="draw_on_training_image_label">Draw Cameras</string>
    <string name="training_capture_label">Training</string>
    <string name="edit_camera_label">Edit Camera</string>
    <string name="licences_label">Licences</string>

    <!--in HistoryActivity-->
    <string name="dont_ask_again">Don\'t ask again</string>
    <string name="permanently_delete_camera">Permanently delete this camera?</string>
    <string name="history_type_text">Type: %s</string>
    <string name="history_area_text">Area: %s</string>
    <string name="history_training_text">Training Capture</string>
    <string name="history_upload_text">Upload: %s</string>



    <!--in DetectorActivity-->
    <string name="manual_capture_button_text">MANUAL</string>

    <string name="general_total_camera_text">Cameras in this area:</string>


    <!--in MapActivity-->
    <plurals name="total_cameras_in_map_text">
        <item quantity="one">camera in this area</item>
        <item quantity="other">cameras in this area</item>
    </plurals>

    <string name="timemachine_text">All cameras until: %s</string>
    <string name="window_upload_text">Camera uploaded on: \n%s</string>


    <!--in OrganizeActivity-->

    <string name="organize_lock_grid">Lock grid + map:</string>
    <string name="organize_center_lat">Center latitude:</string>
    <string name="organize_center_lon">Center longitude:</string>
    <string name="organize_y_size">Height (m):</string>
    <string name="organize_x_size">Length (m):</string>
    <string name="organize_rows">Rows:</string>
    <string name="organize_columns">Columns:</string>

    <string name="organize_reset_button">reset</string>
    <string name="organize_draw_button">Draw Grid</string>
    <string name="organize_back">Back</string>

    <string name="organize_hint_lat">Latitude</string>
    <string name="organize_hint_lon">Longitude</string>
    <string name="organize_hint_length">Length</string>
    <string name="organize_hint_height">Height</string>
    <string name="organize_hint_rows">Rows</string>
    <string name="organize_hint_columns">Columns</string>


    <!--in StatisticsActivity-->

    <plurals name="number_of_cameras_in_area">
        <item quantity="one">camera in your area</item>
        <item quantity="other">cameras in your area</item>
    </plurals>

    <plurals name="captures_by_user">
        <item quantity="one">capture by you</item>
        <item quantity="other">captures by you</item>
    </plurals>

    <string name="added_7d_text">added in the last 7 days</string>
    <string name="added_28d_text">added in the last 28 days</string>
    <string name="global_today_text">added globally today</string>
    <string name="global_28d_text">added globally in the last 28 days</string>
    <string name="global_total_text">cameras global total</string>
    <string name="zero_placeholder_statistics">0</string>

    <!--in EditCameraActivity-->

    <string name="edit_button">EDIT LOCATION</string>
    <string name="save_button">SAVE &amp; GO</string>
    <string name="take_picture_button">TAKE PIC</string>

    <!--in CaptureTrainingImageActivity-->
    <string name="capture">CAPTURE</string>
    <string name="capture_training_image_info">This function allows you to capture images of surveillance cameras to improve the object detection accuracy. After taking the image you will prompted to draw rectangles around surveillance cameras.</string>

    <!--in SettingsActivity-->
    <string name="storage_title">Storage</string>
    <string name="general_title">General</string>
    <string name="synchronization_title">Synchronization</string>
    <string name="map_title">Map</string>
    <string name="capture_title">Capture</string>

    <string name="synchronized_cameras_size">Storage used by synchronized cameras:</string>
    <string name="captured_cameras_size">Storage used by captured cameras:</string>
    <string name="training_cameras_size">Storage used by training cameras:</string>

    <plurals name="cameras_in_database">
        <item quantity="one">%d camera in local database</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d cameras in local database</item>
    </plurals>

    <!--in Tutorials-->

    <string name="tutorial_map_redraw">REDRAW</string>
    <string name="tutorial_map_set_home">SET HOME</string>
    <string name="tutorial_map_message">Please select an area for offline availability</string>

    <string name="tutorial_sync_save_exit">SYNCHRONIZE, SAVE AND EXIT</string>
    <string name="tutorial_save_exit">SAVE AND EXIT</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_interval_text">Synchronization interval:</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_offline_mode_text">Enable offline mode:</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_min_delay_text">Min delay before upload:</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_max_delay_text">Max delay before upload:</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_server_url_hint">Server URL:</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_default_url">https://overpass-api.de/api/interpreter?</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_default_interval">1</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_default_min_delay">6</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_default_max_delay">3</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sync_info_text">- Offline mode disables ALL connections; OpenStreetMap maps will not render and need a x/y/z tile data from th internal storage to work.\n\n
- Synchronization interval is the time between each update from the database server. Uploads will only take place with each synchronization interval. If you choose a long interval uploads might take longer than max delay.\n\n

OPTIONS BELOW ARE DISABLED\n
- Min upload delay specifies the minimum time that has to pass after a camera is captured before the upload happens. This is to protect your privacy by giving you some time to leave the area before the camera appears in the database. You can always manually upload a camera before the time has passed.\n\n
- Max upload delay specifies a limit to how much time passes at the maximum between a camera capture and the upload to the database.</string>


    <string name="tutorial_all_permissions_button">GRANT ALL</string>
    <string name="tutorial_location_permission_button">GRANT LOCATION</string>
    <string name="tutorial_camera_permission_button">GRANT CAMERA</string>
    <string name="tutorial_storage_permission_button">GRANT STORAGE</string>
    <string name="tutorial_permissions_info_text">This application needs some permissions to function properly. Absolutely no personal data is gathered.

- Storage permissions are needed to save images and read map data from your phone\'s storage.\n\n
- Camera permission is needed to use the object detection model to automatically capture surveillance cameras.\n\n
- Location permission is optional, but needed if you want to automatically capture surveillance cameras or center the map on your current position.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_capture_info_text">This application has different methods to capture and map surveillance cameras.
\n\n- By default it uses a self trained object detection model to detect surveillance cameras through the device\'s camera. This mode uses the device\'s orientation and location to calculate the camera position. It\'s most accurate if you move by the camera and capture it from different angles. You can always edit the exact location in your local history before uploading.
\n\n- You can choose to manually capture surveillance cameras. This can be set as the default method.
\n\n- A third way is to capture training images to improve the object detection CURRENTLY NO UPLOAD
\n\n All these options are available via buttons from the default detection method</string>


    <!--in LicencesActivity-->
    <string name="licence_title">Licences:</string>

    <string name="tensorflow_source">Tensorflow Android Example Application</string>
    <string name="osmdroid_source">Osmdroid / OpenStreetMap</string>
    <string name="osmdroidbonus_source">Osmdroid Bonuspack</string>
    <string name="sunders_source">Surveillance Under Surveillance</string>
    <string name="picasso_source">Picasso</string>
    <string name="google_tink_source">Google Tink</string>
    <string name="google_volley_source">Google Volley</string>




    <!-- LICENCES -->

    <string name="sunders_licence">This project has been inspired by \nhttps://sunders.uber.space , new and more intrusive laws and the increasing amount of everyday surveillance\n

    </string>


    <string name="tensorflow_licence">https://github.com/tensorflow/tensorflow/tree/master/tensorflow/examples/android \n\nCopyright 2016 The TensorFlow Authors. All Rights Reserved.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.\n\nCopyright 2017 The Android Open Source Project
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at
      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.</string>

    <string name="osmdroid_licence">© OpenStreetMap contributors\nhttps://www.openstreetmap.org/copyright\n\nhttps://github.com/osmdroid/osmdroid\n\nApache License
                           Version 2.0, January 2004
                        http://www.apache.org/licenses/

   TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

   1. Definitions.

      \"License\" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,
      and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.

      \"Licensor\" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by
      the copyright owner that is granting the License.

      \"Legal Entity\" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all
      other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common
      control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,
      \"control\" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the
      direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or
      otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the
      outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.

      \"You\" (or \"Your\") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity
      exercising permissions granted by this License.

      \"Source\" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,
      including but not limited to software source code, documentation
      source, and configuration files.

      \"Object\" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical
      transformation or translation of a Source form, including but
      not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,
      and conversions to other media types.

      \"Work\" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or
      Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a
      copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work
      (an example is provided in the Appendix below).

      \"Derivative Works\" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object
      form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the
      editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications
      represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes
      of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain
      separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,
      the Work and Derivative Works thereof.

      \"Contribution\" shall mean any work of authorship, including
      the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions
      to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally
      submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner
      or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of
      the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, \"submitted\"
      means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent
      to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to
      communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,
      and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the
      Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but
      excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise
      designated in writing by the copyright owner as \"Not a Contribution.\"

      \"Contributor\" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity
      on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and
      subsequently incorporated within the Work.

   2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
      this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
      worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
      copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,
      publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the
      Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.

   3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
      this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
      worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
      (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,
      use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,
      where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable
      by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their
      Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)
      with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You
      institute patent litigation against any entity (including a
      cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work
      or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct
      or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses
      granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate
      as of the date such litigation is filed.

   4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the
      Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without
      modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You
      meet the following conditions:

      (a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or
          Derivative Works a copy of this License; and

      (b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices
          stating that You changed the files; and

      (c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works
          that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and
          attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,
          excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of
          the Derivative Works; and

      (d) If the Work includes a \"NOTICE\" text file as part of its
          distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must
          include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained
          within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not
          pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one
          of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed
          as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or
          documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,
          within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and
          wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents
          of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and
          do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution
          notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside
          or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided
          that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed
          as modifying the License.

      You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and
      may provide additional or different license terms and conditions
      for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or
      for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,
      reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with
      the conditions stated in this License.

   5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,
      any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work
      by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of
      this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
      Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify
      the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed
      with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

   6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade
      names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,
      except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the
      origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

   7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or
      agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each
      Contributor provides its Contributions) on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
      WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
      implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions
      of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A
      PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the
      appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any
      risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

   8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,
      whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,
      unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly
      negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
      liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
      incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a
      result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the
      Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,
      work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all
      other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor
      has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

   9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing
      the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,
      and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,
      or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this
      License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only
      on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf
      of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,
      defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability
      incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason
      of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

   END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS</string>


    <string name="osmdroid_bonuspack_licence">https://github.com/MKergall/osmbonuspack\n\nGNU LESSER GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007

Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. http://fsf.org/ Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.

This version of the GNU Lesser General Public License incorporates the terms and conditions of version 3 of the GNU General Public License, supplemented by the additional permissions listed below.

    Additional Definitions.

As used herein, \"this License\" refers to version 3 of the GNU Lesser General Public License, and the \"GNU GPL\" refers to version 3 of the GNU General Public License.

\"The Library\" refers to a covered work governed by this License, other than an Application or a Combined Work as defined below.

An \"Application\" is any work that makes use of an interface provided by the Library, but which is not otherwise based on the Library. Defining a subclass of a class defined by the Library is deemed a mode of using an interface provided by the Library.

A \"Combined Work\" is a work produced by combining or linking an Application with the Library. The particular version of the Library with which the Combined Work was made is also called the \"Linked Version\".

The \"Minimal Corresponding Source\" for a Combined Work means the Corresponding Source for the Combined Work, excluding any source code for portions of the Combined Work that, considered in isolation, are based on the Application, and not on the Linked Version.

The \"Corresponding Application Code\" for a Combined Work means the object code and/or source code for the Application, including any data and utility programs needed for reproducing the Combined Work from the Application, but excluding the System Libraries of the Combined Work.

    Exception to Section 3 of the GNU GPL.

You may convey a covered work under sections 3 and 4 of this License without being bound by section 3 of the GNU GPL.

    Conveying Modified Versions.

If you modify a copy of the Library, and, in your modifications, a facility refers to a function or data to be supplied by an Application that uses the facility (other than as an argument passed when the facility is invoked), then you may convey a copy of the modified version:

a) under this License, provided that you make a good faith effort to ensure that, in the event an Application does not supply the function or data, the facility still operates, and performs whatever part of its purpose remains meaningful, or

b) under the GNU GPL, with none of the additional permissions of this License applicable to that copy.

    Object Code Incorporating Material from Library Header Files.

The object code form of an Application may incorporate material from a header file that is part of the Library. You may convey such object code under terms of your choice, provided that, if the incorporated material is not limited to numerical parameters, data structure layouts and accessors, or small macros, inline functions and templates (ten or fewer lines in length), you do both of the following:

a) Give prominent notice with each copy of the object code that the Library is used in it and that the Library and its use are covered by this License.

b) Accompany the object code with a copy of the GNU GPL and this license document.

    Combined Works.

You may convey a Combined Work under terms of your choice that, taken together, effectively do not restrict modification of the portions of the Library contained in the Combined Work and reverse engineering for debugging such modifications, if you also do each of the following:

a) Give prominent notice with each copy of the Combined Work that the Library is used in it and that the Library and its use are covered by this License.

b) Accompany the Combined Work with a copy of the GNU GPL and this license document.

c) For a Combined Work that displays copyright notices during execution, include the copyright notice for the Library among these notices, as well as a reference directing the user to the copies of the GNU GPL and this license document.

d) Do one of the following:

   0) Convey the Minimal Corresponding Source under the terms of this
   License, and the Corresponding Application Code in a form
   suitable for, and under terms that permit, the user to
   recombine or relink the Application with a modified version of
   the Linked Version to produce a modified Combined Work, in the
   manner specified by section 6 of the GNU GPL for conveying
   Corresponding Source.

   1) Use a suitable shared library mechanism for linking with the
   Library.  A suitable mechanism is one that (a) uses at run time
   a copy of the Library already present on the user\'s computer
   system, and (b) will operate properly with a modified version
   of the Library that is interface-compatible with the Linked
   Version.

e) Provide Installation Information, but only if you would otherwise be required to provide such information under section 6 of the GNU GPL, and only to the extent that such information is necessary to install and execute a modified version of the Combined Work produced by recombining or relinking the Application with a modified version of the Linked Version. (If you use option 4d0, the Installation Information must accompany the Minimal Corresponding Source and Corresponding Application Code. If you use option 4d1, you must provide the Installation Information in the manner specified by section 6 of the GNU GPL for conveying Corresponding Source.)

    Combined Libraries.

You may place library facilities that are a work based on the Library side by side in a single library together with other library facilities that are not Applications and are not covered by this License, and convey such a combined library under terms of your choice, if you do both of the following:

a) Accompany the combined library with a copy of the same work based on the Library, uncombined with any other library facilities, conveyed under the terms of this License.

b) Give prominent notice with the combined library that part of it is a work based on the Library, and explaining where to find the accompanying uncombined form of the same work.

    Revised Versions of the GNU Lesser General Public License.

The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or new versions of the GNU Lesser General Public License from time to time. Such new versions will be similar in spirit to the present version, but may differ in detail to address new problems or concerns.

Each version is given a distinguishing version number. If the Library as you received it specifies that a certain numbered version of the GNU Lesser General Public License \"or any later version\" applies to it, you have the option of following the terms and conditions either of that published version or of any later version published by the Free Software Foundation. If the Library as you received it does not specify a version number of the GNU Lesser General Public License, you may choose any version of the GNU Lesser General Public License ever published by the Free Software Foundation.

If the Library as you received it specifies that a proxy can decide whether future versions of the GNU Lesser General Public License shall apply, that proxy\'s public statement of acceptance of any version is permanent authorization for you to choose that version for the Library.
    </string>

    <string name="picasso_licence">https://square.github.io/picasso/\n\nCopyright 2013 Square, Inc.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.</string>

    <string name="google_tink_licence">https://github.com/google/tink\n\nApache License
                           Version 2.0, January 2004
                        http://www.apache.org/licenses/

   TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

   1. Definitions.

      \"License\" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,
      and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.

      \"Licensor\" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by
      the copyright owner that is granting the License.

      \"Legal Entity\" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all
      other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common
      control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,
      \"control\" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the
      direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or
      otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the
      outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.

      \"You\" (or \"Your\") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity
      exercising permissions granted by this License.

      \"Source\" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,
      including but not limited to software source code, documentation
      source, and configuration files.

      \"Object\" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical
      transformation or translation of a Source form, including but
      not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,
      and conversions to other media types.

      \"Work\" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or
      Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a
      copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work
      (an example is provided in the Appendix below).

      \"Derivative Works\" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object
      form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the
      editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications
      represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes
      of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain
      separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,
      the Work and Derivative Works thereof.

      \"Contribution\" shall mean any work of authorship, including
      the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions
      to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally
      submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner
      or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of
      the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, \"submitted\"
      means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent
      to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to
      communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,
      and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the
      Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but
      excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise
      designated in writing by the copyright owner as \"Not a Contribution.\"

      \"Contributor\" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity
      on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and
      subsequently incorporated within the Work.

   2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
      this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
      worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
      copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,
      publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the
      Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.

   3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
      this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
      worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
      (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,
      use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,
      where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable
      by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their
      Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)
      with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You
      institute patent litigation against any entity (including a
      cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work
      or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct
      or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses
      granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate
      as of the date such litigation is filed.

   4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the
      Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without
      modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You
      meet the following conditions:

      (a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or
          Derivative Works a copy of this License; and

      (b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices
          stating that You changed the files; and

      (c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works
          that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and
          attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,
          excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of
          the Derivative Works; and

      (d) If the Work includes a \"NOTICE\" text file as part of its
          distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must
          include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained
          within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not
          pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one
          of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed
          as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or
          documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,
          within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and
          wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents
          of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and
          do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution
          notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside
          or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided
          that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed
          as modifying the License.

      You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and
      may provide additional or different license terms and conditions
      for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or
      for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,
      reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with
      the conditions stated in this License.

   5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,
      any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work
      by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of
      this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
      Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify
      the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed
      with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

   6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade
      names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,
      except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the
      origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

   7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or
      agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each
      Contributor provides its Contributions) on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
      WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
      implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions
      of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A
      PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the
      appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any
      risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

   8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,
      whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,
      unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly
      negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
      liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
      incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a
      result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the
      Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,
      work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all
      other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor
      has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

   9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing
      the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,
      and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,
      or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this
      License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only
      on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf
      of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,
      defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability
      incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason
      of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

   END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS</string>

    <string name="google_volley_licence">https://github.com/google/volley/\n\nApache License
                           Version 2.0, January 2004
                        http://www.apache.org/licenses/

   TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

   1. Definitions.

      \"License\" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,
      and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.

      \"Licensor\" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by
      the copyright owner that is granting the License.

      \"Legal Entity\" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all
      other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common
      control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,
      \"control\" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the
      direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or
      otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the
      outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.

      \"You\" (or \"Your\") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity
      exercising permissions granted by this License.

      \"Source\" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,
      including but not limited to software source code, documentation
      source, and configuration files.

      \"Object\" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical
      transformation or translation of a Source form, including but
      not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,
      and conversions to other media types.

      \"Work\" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or
      Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a
      copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work
      (an example is provided in the Appendix below).

      \"Derivative Works\" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object
      form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the
      editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications
      represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes
      of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain
      separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,
      the Work and Derivative Works thereof.

      \"Contribution\" shall mean any work of authorship, including
      the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions
      to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally
      submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner
      or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of
      the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, \"submitted\"
      means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent
      to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to
      communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,
      and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the
      Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but
      excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise
      designated in writing by the copyright owner as \"Not a Contribution.\"

      \"Contributor\" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity
      on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and
      subsequently incorporated within the Work.

   2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
      this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
      worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
      copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,
      publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the
      Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.

   3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
      this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
      worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
      (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,
      use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,
      where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable
      by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their
      Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)
      with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You
      institute patent litigation against any entity (including a
      cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work
      or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct
      or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses
      granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate
      as of the date such litigation is filed.

   4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the
      Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without
      modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You
      meet the following conditions:

      (a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or
          Derivative Works a copy of this License; and

      (b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices
          stating that You changed the files; and

      (c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works
          that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and
          attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,
          excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of
          the Derivative Works; and

      (d) If the Work includes a \"NOTICE\" text file as part of its
          distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must
          include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained
          within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not
          pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one
          of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed
          as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or
          documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,
          within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and
          wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents
          of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and
          do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution
          notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside
          or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided
          that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed
          as modifying the License.

      You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and
      may provide additional or different license terms and conditions
      for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or
      for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,
      reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with
      the conditions stated in this License.

   5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,
      any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work
      by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of
      this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
      Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify
      the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed
      with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

   6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade
      names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,
      except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the
      origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

   7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or
      agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each
      Contributor provides its Contributions) on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,
      WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
      implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions
      of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A
      PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the
      appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any
      risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

   8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,
      whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,
      unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly
      negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
      liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
      incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a
      result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the
      Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,
      work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all
      other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor
      has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

   9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing
      the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,
      and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,
      or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this
      License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only
      on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf
      of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,
      defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability
      incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason
      of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

   END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS</string>






</resources>
